{
    "en": {
        "SKILL_WELCOME":"Welcome to AskPlex. What would you like to do?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_REPROMPT": "What would you like to do?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK": "Welcome to AskPlex, you were listening to {}. Would you like to resume?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK_REPROMPT": "Would you like to resume?",
        "SKILL_HELP": "AskPlex connects to your Plex server, you can ask me for music by artist, album or genre, as well as specific songs and playlists",
        "SKILL_INTENT_SLOTS_MISSING": "Sorry, I didn't catch that.",
        "SKILL_EXCEPTION": "Sorry, an internal error occurred",
        "SKILL_DEVICE_NOT_SUPPORTED": "Sorry, this device is not supported",
        "SKILL_SONG_DETAILS": "This is {song} by {artist}",
        "PMS_CONNECTION_ERROR": "Sorry, there was an error when connecting to the plex media server",
        "PMS_SECTION_ERROR": "Sorry, there was an error when searching for the section {}",
        "PMS_SECTION_NOT_FOUND": "Sorry, I can't find the section {}",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_ERROR": "Sorry, there was an error when searching for music",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Sorry, I can't find music in your collection",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "Sorry, there was an error when searching for {}",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Sorry, I can't find {} in your collection",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_ERROR": "Sorry, there was an error when searching for the song {song} by {artist}",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Sorry, I can't find the song {song} by {artist} in your collection",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_ERROR": "Sorry, there was an error when searching for the album {album} by {artist}",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Sorry, the album {album} by {artist} doesn't have any tracks",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_ERROR": "Sorry, there was an error when searching for {} music",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Sorry, I can't find {} music in your collection",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "Sorry, there was an error when searching for the playlist {}",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Sorry, I can't find the playlist {}",
        "PMS_PLAYING": "Playing {} in AsPlex",
        "PMS_PLNAME_RANDOM_MUSIC": "Random music",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_ARTIST": "music by {}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_SONG": "{song} by {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_ALBUM": "the album {album} by {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_GENRE": "{} music",
        "PMS_PLNAME_PLAYLIST": "the playlist {}"
    },
    "es": {
        "SKILL_WELCOME":"Bienvenido a AskPlex. Qué quieres hacer?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_REPROMPT": "Qué quieres hacer?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK": "Bienvenido AskPlex, estabas escuchando {}. Quieres continuar?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK_REPROMPT": "Quieres continuar?",
        "SKILL_HELP": "AskPlex conecta con tu servidor plex, puedes pedirme música por artista, álbum o género, así como canciones especificas y listas de reproducción",
        "SKILL_INTENT_SLOTS_MISSING": "Disculpa, no te entendí",
        "SKILL_EXCEPTION": "Disculpa, ha ocurrido un error interno",
        "SKILL_DEVICE_NOT_SUPPORTED": "Disculpa, este dispositivo no está soportado",
        "SKILL_SONG_DETAILS": "Esto es {song} de {artist}",
        "PMS_CONNECTION_ERROR": "Disculpa, ha ocurrido un error al conectar con el servidor de medios plex",
        "PMS_SECTION_ERROR": "Disculpa, ha ocurrido un error al buscar la sección {}",
        "PMS_SECTION_NOT_FOUND": "Disculpa, no encontré la sección {}",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_ERROR": "Disculpa, ha ocurrido un error al buscar música",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Disculpa, no encuentro musica en tu colección",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "Disculpa, ha ocurrido un error al buscar a {}",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Disculpa, no encuentro a {} en tu colección",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_ERROR": "Disculpa, ha ocurrido un error al buscar la canción {song} de {artist}",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Disculpa, no encuentro la canción {song} de {artist} en tu colección",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_ERROR": "Disculpa, ha ocurrido un error al buscar el álbum {album} de {artist}",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Disculpa, el álbum {album} de {artist} no contiene canciones",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_ERROR": "Disculpa, ha ocurrido un error al buscar música {}",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Disculpa, no encuentro música {} en tu colección",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "Disculpa, ha ocurrido un error al buscar la lista de reproducción {}",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Disculpa, no encuentro la lista de reproducción {}",
        "PMS_PLAYING": "Reproduciendo {} en AskPlex",
        "PMS_PLNAME_RANDOM_MUSIC": "música aleatoria",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_ARTIST": "música de {}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_SONG": "{song} de {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_ALBUM": "el álbum {album} de {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_GENRE": "música {}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_PLAYLIST": "la lista de reproducción {}"
    },
    "es-ES": {
        "SKILL_WELCOME": "Bienvenido a AskPlex. Qué te gustaría hacer?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_REPROMPT": "Qué te gustaría hacer?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK": "Bienvenido a AskPlex, estabas escuchando {}. Te gustaría reanudar?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK_REPROMPT": "Te gustaría reanudar?",
        "SKILL_HELP": "AskPlex se conecta a tu servidor Plex, puedes pedirme música por artista, álbum o género, así como canciones y listas de reproducción específicas",
        "SKILL_INTENT_SLOTS_MISSING": "Lo siento, no entendí eso",
        "SKILL_EXCEPTION": "Lo siento, ha ocurrido un error interno",
        "SKILL_DEVICE_NOT_SUPPORTED": "Lo siento, este dispositivo no es compatible",
        "SKILL_SONG_DETAILS": "Esto es {song} de {artist}",
        "PMS_CONNECTION_ERROR": "Lo siento, hubo un error al conectar con el servidor de medios Plex",
        "PMS_SECTION_ERROR": "Lo siento, hubo un error al buscar la sección {}",
        "PMS_SECTION_NOT_FOUND": "Lo siento, no puedo encontrar la sección {}",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_ERROR": "Lo siento, hubo un error al buscar música",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Lo siento, no puedo encontrar música en tu colección",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "Lo siento, hubo un error al buscar a {}",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Lo siento, no puedo encontrar a {} en tu colección",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_ERROR": "Lo siento, hubo un error al buscar la canción {song} de {artist}",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Lo siento, no puedo encontrar la canción {song} de {artist} en tu colección",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_ERROR": "Lo siento, hubo un error al buscar el álbum {album} de {artist}",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Lo siento, el álbum {album} de {artist} no tiene ninguna pista",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_ERROR": "Lo siento, hubo un error al buscar música de {}",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Lo siento, no puedo encontrar música de {} en tu colección",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "Lo siento, hubo un error al buscar la lista de reproducción {}",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Lo siento, no puedo encontrar la lista de reproducción {}",
        "PMS_PLAYING": "Reproduciendo {} en AsPlex",
        "PMS_PLNAME_RANDOM_MUSIC": "Música aleatoria",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_ARTIST": "música de {}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_SONG": "{song} de {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_ALBUM": "el álbum {album} de {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_GENRE": "música de {}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_PLAYLIST": "la lista de reproducción {}"
    },
    "fr": {
        "SKILL_WELCOME": "Bienvenue sur AskPlex. Que souhaitez-vous faire ?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_REPROMPT": "Que souhaitez-vous faire ?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK": "Bienvenue sur AskPlex, vous écoutiez {}. Souhaitez-vous reprendre ?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK_REPROMPT": "Souhaitez-vous reprendre ?",
        "SKILL_HELP": "AskPlex se connecte à votre serveur Plex, vous pouvez me demander de la musique par artiste, album ou genre, ainsi que des chansons et des playlists spécifiques.",
        "SKILL_INTENT_SLOTS_MISSING": "Désolé, je n'ai pas bien compris.",
        "SKILL_EXCEPTION": "Désolé, une erreur interne est survenue.",
        "SKILL_DEVICE_NOT_SUPPORTED": "Désolé, cet appareil n'est pas pris en charge.",
        "SKILL_SONG_DETAILS": "C'est {song} de {artist}.",
        "PMS_CONNECTION_ERROR": "Désolé, une erreur s'est produite lors de la connexion au serveur Plex.",
        "PMS_SECTION_ERROR": "Désolé, une erreur est survenue lors de la recherche de la section {}.",
        "PMS_SECTION_NOT_FOUND": "Désolé, je ne trouve pas la section {}.",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_ERROR": "Désolé, une erreur est survenue lors de la recherche de musique.",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Désolé, je ne trouve pas de musique dans votre collection.",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "Désolé, une erreur est survenue lors de la recherche de {}.",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Désolé, je ne trouve pas {} dans votre collection.",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_ERROR": "Désolé, une erreur est survenue lors de la recherche de la chanson {song} de {artist}.",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Désolé, je ne trouve pas la chanson {song} de {artist} dans votre collection.",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_ERROR": "Désolé, une erreur est survenue lors de la recherche de l'album {album} de {artist}.",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Désolé, l'album {album} de {artist} ne contient pas de morceaux.",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_ERROR": "Désolé, une erreur est survenue lors de la recherche de musique {}.",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Désolé, je ne trouve pas de musique {} dans votre collection.",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "Désolé, une erreur est survenue lors de la recherche de la playlist {}.",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Désolé, je ne trouve pas la playlist {}.",
        "PMS_PLAYING": "Lecture de {} sur AskPlex.",
        "PMS_PLNAME_RANDOM_MUSIC": "Musique aléatoire",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_ARTIST": "musique de {}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_SONG": "{song} de {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_ALBUM": "l'album {album} de {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_GENRE": "musique {}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_PLAYLIST": "la playlist {}"
    },
    "pt-BR": {
        "SKILL_WELCOME": "Bem-vindo ao AskPlex. O que você gostaria de fazer?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_REPROMPT": "O que você gostaria de fazer?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK": "Bem-vindo ao AskPlex, você estava ouvindo {}. Gostaria de retomar?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK_REPROMPT": "Gostaria de retomar?",
        "SKILL_HELP": "O AskPlex se conecta ao seu servidor Plex, você pode me pedir músicas por artista, álbum ou gênero, além de músicas e playlists específicas.",
        "SKILL_INTENT_SLOTS_MISSING": "Desculpe, não entendi.",
        "SKILL_EXCEPTION": "Desculpe, ocorreu um erro interno.",
        "SKILL_DEVICE_NOT_SUPPORTED": "Desculpe, este dispositivo não é suportado.",
        "SKILL_SONG_DETAILS": "Esta é {song} de {artist}.",
        "PMS_CONNECTION_ERROR": "Desculpe, ocorreu um erro ao conectar ao servidor Plex.",
        "PMS_SECTION_ERROR": "Desculpe, ocorreu um erro ao buscar a seção {}.",
        "PMS_SECTION_NOT_FOUND": "Desculpe, não consigo encontrar a seção {}.",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_ERROR": "Desculpe, ocorreu um erro ao buscar músicas.",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Desculpe, não consigo encontrar músicas na sua coleção.",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "Desculpe, ocorreu um erro ao buscar por {}.",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Desculpe, não consigo encontrar {} na sua coleção.",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_ERROR": "Desculpe, ocorreu um erro ao buscar a música {song} de {artist}.",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Desculpe, não consigo encontrar a música {song} de {artist} na sua coleção.",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_ERROR": "Desculpe, ocorreu um erro ao buscar o álbum {album} de {artist}.",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Desculpe, o álbum {album} de {artist} não tem faixas.",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_ERROR": "Desculpe, ocorreu um erro ao buscar música de {}.",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Desculpe, não consigo encontrar músicas de {} na sua coleção.",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "Desculpe, ocorreu um erro ao buscar a playlist {}.",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Desculpe, não consigo encontrar a playlist {}.",
        "PMS_PLAYING": "Reproduzindo {} no AskPlex.",
        "PMS_PLNAME_RANDOM_MUSIC": "Música aleatória",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_ARTIST": "música de {}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_SONG": "{song} de {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_ALBUM": "o álbum {album} de {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_GENRE": "música de {}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_PLAYLIST": "a playlist {}"
    },
    "it-IT": {
        "SKILL_WELCOME": "Benvenuto su AskPlex. Cosa vorresti fare?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_REPROMPT": "Cosa vorresti fare?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK": "Benvenuto su AskPlex, stavi ascoltando {}. Vuoi riprendere?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK_REPROMPT": "Vuoi riprendere?",
        "SKILL_HELP": "AskPlex si connette al tuo server Plex, puoi chiedermi della musica per artista, album o genere, oltre a canzoni e playlist specifiche",
        "SKILL_INTENT_SLOTS_MISSING": "Mi dispiace, non ho capito.",
        "SKILL_EXCEPTION": "Mi dispiace, si è verificato un errore interno",
        "SKILL_DEVICE_NOT_SUPPORTED": "Mi dispiace, questo dispositivo non è supportato",
        "SKILL_SONG_DETAILS": "Questa è {song} di {artist}",
        "PMS_CONNECTION_ERROR": "Mi dispiace, c'è stato un errore durante la connessione al server Plex",
        "PMS_SECTION_ERROR": "Mi dispiace, c'è stato un errore durante la ricerca della sezione {}",
        "PMS_SECTION_NOT_FOUND": "Mi dispiace, non riesco a trovare la sezione {}",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_ERROR": "Mi dispiace, c'è stato un errore durante la ricerca della musica",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Mi dispiace, non riesco a trovare musica nella tua collezione",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "Mi dispiace, c'è stato un errore durante la ricerca di {}",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Mi dispiace, non riesco a trovare {} nella tua collezione",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_ERROR": "Mi dispiace, c'è stato un errore durante la ricerca della canzone {song} di {artist}",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Mi dispiace, non riesco a trovare la canzone {song} di {artist} nella tua collezione",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_ERROR": "Mi dispiace, c'è stato un errore durante la ricerca dell'album {album} di {artist}",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Mi dispiace, l'album {album} di {artist} non ha tracce",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_ERROR": "Mi dispiace, c'è stato un errore durante la ricerca della musica {}",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Mi dispiace, non riesco a trovare musica {} nella tua collezione",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "Mi dispiace, c'è stato un errore durante la ricerca della playlist {}",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Mi dispiace, non riesco a trovare la playlist {}",
        "PMS_PLAYING": "Sto riproducendo {} in AsPlex",
        "PMS_PLNAME_RANDOM_MUSIC": "Musica casuale",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_ARTIST": "musica di {}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_SONG": "{song} di {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_ALBUM": "l'album {album} di {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_GENRE": "musica {}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_PLAYLIST": "la playlist {}"
    },
    "de-DE": {
        "SKILL_WELCOME": "Willkommen bei AskPlex. Was möchten Sie tun?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_REPROMPT": "Was möchten Sie tun?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK": "Willkommen bei AskPlex, Sie haben gerade {} gehört. Möchten Sie fortfahren?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK_REPROMPT": "Möchten Sie fortfahren?",
        "SKILL_HELP": "AskPlex verbindet sich mit Ihrem Plex-Server. Sie können mich nach Musik von Künstlern, Alben oder Genres fragen, sowie nach bestimmten Songs und Playlists.",
        "SKILL_INTENT_SLOTS_MISSING": "Entschuldigung, das habe ich nicht verstanden.",
        "SKILL_EXCEPTION": "Entschuldigung, ein interner Fehler ist aufgetreten.",
        "SKILL_DEVICE_NOT_SUPPORTED": "Entschuldigung, dieses Gerät wird nicht unterstützt.",
        "SKILL_SONG_DETAILS": "Dies ist {song} von {artist}.",
        "PMS_CONNECTION_ERROR": "Entschuldigung, es gab einen Fehler bei der Verbindung zum Plex-Server.",
        "PMS_SECTION_ERROR": "Entschuldigung, es gab einen Fehler bei der Suche nach der Sektion {}.",
        "PMS_SECTION_NOT_FOUND": "Entschuldigung, ich kann die Sektion {} nicht finden.",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_ERROR": "Entschuldigung, es gab einen Fehler bei der Musiksuche.",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Entschuldigung, ich kann keine Musik in Ihrer Sammlung finden.",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "Entschuldigung, es gab einen Fehler bei der Suche nach {}.",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Entschuldigung, ich kann {} nicht in Ihrer Sammlung finden.",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_ERROR": "Entschuldigung, es gab einen Fehler bei der Suche nach dem Song {song} von {artist}.",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Entschuldigung, ich kann den Song {song} von {artist} nicht in Ihrer Sammlung finden.",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_ERROR": "Entschuldigung, es gab einen Fehler bei der Suche nach dem Album {album} von {artist}.",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Entschuldigung, das Album {album} von {artist} hat keine Titel.",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_ERROR": "Entschuldigung, es gab einen Fehler bei der Suche nach Musik von {}.",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Entschuldigung, ich kann keine Musik von {} in Ihrer Sammlung finden.",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "Entschuldigung, es gab einen Fehler bei der Suche nach der Playlist {}.",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Entschuldigung, ich kann die Playlist {} nicht finden.",
        "PMS_PLAYING": "Wiedergabe von {} in AskPlex.",
        "PMS_PLNAME_RANDOM_MUSIC": "Zufallsmusik",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_ARTIST": "Musik von {}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_SONG": "{song} von {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_ALBUM": "das Album {album} von {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_GENRE": "Musik von {}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_PLAYLIST": "die Playlist {}"
    },
    "nl-NL": {
        "SKILL_WELCOME": "Welkom bij AskPlex. Wat zou je willen doen?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_REPROMPT": "Wat zou je willen doen?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK": "Welkom bij AskPlex, je luisterde naar {}. Wil je doorgaan?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK_REPROMPT": "Wil je doorgaan?",
        "SKILL_HELP": "AskPlex maakt verbinding met je Plex-server. Je kunt me vragen om muziek op artiest, album of genre, evenals specifieke nummers en afspeellijsten.",
        "SKILL_INTENT_SLOTS_MISSING": "Sorry, dat heb ik niet begrepen.",
        "SKILL_EXCEPTION": "Sorry, er is een interne fout opgetreden.",
        "SKILL_DEVICE_NOT_SUPPORTED": "Sorry, dit apparaat wordt niet ondersteund.",
        "SKILL_SONG_DETAILS": "Dit is {song} van {artist}.",
        "PMS_CONNECTION_ERROR": "Sorry, er is een fout opgetreden bij het verbinden met de Plex-server.",
        "PMS_SECTION_ERROR": "Sorry, er is een fout opgetreden bij het zoeken naar sectie {}.",
        "PMS_SECTION_NOT_FOUND": "Sorry, ik kan de sectie {} niet vinden.",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_ERROR": "Sorry, er is een fout opgetreden bij het zoeken naar muziek.",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Sorry, ik kan geen muziek in je collectie vinden.",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "Sorry, er is een fout opgetreden bij het zoeken naar {}.",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Sorry, ik kan {} niet vinden in je collectie.",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_ERROR": "Sorry, er is een fout opgetreden bij het zoeken naar het nummer {song} van {artist}.",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Sorry, ik kan het nummer {song} van {artist} niet vinden in je collectie.",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_ERROR": "Sorry, er is een fout opgetreden bij het zoeken naar het album {album} van {artist}.",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Sorry, het album {album} van {artist} heeft geen nummers.",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_ERROR": "Sorry, er is een fout opgetreden bij het zoeken naar muziek van {}.",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Sorry, ik kan geen muziek van {} vinden in je collectie.",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "Sorry, er is een fout opgetreden bij het zoeken naar de afspeellijst {}.",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "Sorry, ik kan de afspeellijst {} niet vinden.",
        "PMS_PLAYING": "Afspelen van {} in AskPlex.",
        "PMS_PLNAME_RANDOM_MUSIC": "Willekeurige muziek",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_ARTIST": "muziek van {}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_SONG": "{song} van {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_ALBUM": "het album {album} van {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_GENRE": "muziek van {}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_PLAYLIST": "de afspeellijst {}"
    },
    "ja-JP": {
        "SKILL_WELCOME": "AskPlexへようこそ。何をしたいですか？",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_REPROMPT": "何をしたいですか？",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK": "AskPlexへようこそ、あなたは{}を聞いていました。再開しますか？",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK_REPROMPT": "再開しますか？",
        "SKILL_HELP": "AskPlexはあなたのPlexサーバーに接続します。アーティスト、アルバム、またはジャンルで音楽をリクエストしたり、特定の曲やプレイリストをリクエストしたりできます。",
        "SKILL_INTENT_SLOTS_MISSING": "すみません、わかりませんでした。",
        "SKILL_EXCEPTION": "すみません、内部エラーが発生しました。",
        "SKILL_DEVICE_NOT_SUPPORTED": "すみません、このデバイスはサポートされていません。",
        "SKILL_SONG_DETAILS": "これは{song}、{artist}によるものです。",
        "PMS_CONNECTION_ERROR": "すみません、Plexメディアサーバーへの接続中にエラーが発生しました。",
        "PMS_SECTION_ERROR": "すみません、セクション{}を検索中にエラーが発生しました。",
        "PMS_SECTION_NOT_FOUND": "すみません、セクション{}が見つかりません。",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_ERROR": "すみません、音楽を検索中にエラーが発生しました。",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_EMPTY": "すみません、あなたのコレクションに音楽が見つかりません。",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "すみません、{}を検索中にエラーが発生しました。",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "すみません、あなたのコレクションに{}が見つかりません。",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_ERROR": "すみません、{song} by {artist}の曲を検索中にエラーが発生しました。",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_EMPTY": "すみません、あなたのコレクションに{song} by {artist}の曲が見つかりません。",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_ERROR": "すみません、{album} by {artist}のアルバムを検索中にエラーが発生しました。",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_EMPTY": "すみません、{album} by {artist}のアルバムには曲がありません。",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_ERROR": "すみません、{}の音楽を検索中にエラーが発生しました。",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_EMPTY": "すみません、あなたのコレクションに{}の音楽が見つかりません。",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "すみません、{}のプレイリストを検索中にエラーが発生しました。",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "すみません、{}のプレイリストが見つかりません。",
        "PMS_PLAYING": "AskPlexで{}を再生中。",
        "PMS_PLNAME_RANDOM_MUSIC": "ランダムミュージック",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_ARTIST": "{}の音楽",
        "PMS_PLNAME_SONG": "{song} by {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_ALBUM": "{artist}のアルバム{album}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_GENRE": "{}の音楽",
        "PMS_PLNAME_PLAYLIST": "{}のプレイリスト"
    },
    "hi-IN": {
        "SKILL_WELCOME": "AskPlex में स्वागत है। आप क्या करना चाहेंगे?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_REPROMPT": "आप क्या करना चाहेंगे?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK": "AskPlex में स्वागत है, आप {} सुन रहे थे। क्या आप फिर से शुरू करना चाहेंगे?",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK_REPROMPT": "क्या आप फिर से शुरू करना चाहेंगे?",
        "SKILL_HELP": "AskPlex आपके Plex सर्वर से कनेक्ट होता है, आप मुझसे कलाकार, एल्बम या शैली के हिसाब से संगीत पूछ सकते हैं, साथ ही विशिष्ट गाने और प्लेलिस्ट भी पूछ सकते हैं।",
        "SKILL_INTENT_SLOTS_MISSING": "मुझे खेद है, मैंने वह नहीं सुना।",
        "SKILL_EXCEPTION": "मुझे खेद है, एक आंतरिक त्रुटि हुई है।",
        "SKILL_DEVICE_NOT_SUPPORTED": "मुझे खेद है, यह डिवाइस समर्थित नहीं है।",
        "SKILL_SONG_DETAILS": "यह {song} है, {artist} द्वारा।",
        "PMS_CONNECTION_ERROR": "मुझे खेद है, Plex मीडिया सर्वर से कनेक्ट करते समय त्रुटि हुई।",
        "PMS_SECTION_ERROR": "मुझे खेद है, {} सेक्शन को खोजते समय त्रुटि हुई।",
        "PMS_SECTION_NOT_FOUND": "मुझे खेद है, {} सेक्शन नहीं मिल पाया।",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_ERROR": "मुझे खेद है, संगीत खोजते समय त्रुटि हुई।",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_EMPTY": "मुझे खेद है, आपकी संग्रह में कोई संगीत नहीं मिल रहा है।",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "मुझे खेद है, {} के लिए खोज करते समय त्रुटि हुई।",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "मुझे खेद है, आपकी संग्रह में {} नहीं मिल रहा है।",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_ERROR": "मुझे खेद है, {song} by {artist} गीत को खोजते समय त्रुटि हुई।",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_EMPTY": "मुझे खेद है, {song} by {artist} गीत आपकी संग्रह में नहीं मिला।",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_ERROR": "मुझे खेद है, {album} by {artist} एल्बम को खोजते समय त्रुटि हुई।",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_EMPTY": "मुझे खेद है, {album} by {artist} एल्बम में कोई ट्रैक नहीं हैं।",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_ERROR": "मुझे खेद है, {} संगीत को खोजते समय त्रुटि हुई।",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_EMPTY": "मुझे खेद है, आपकी संग्रह में {} संगीत नहीं मिल रहा है।",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "मुझे खेद है, {} प्लेलिस्ट को खोजते समय त्रुटि हुई।",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "मुझे खेद है, {} प्लेलिस्ट नहीं मिल रहा है।",
        "PMS_PLAYING": "AskPlex में {} चल रहा है।",
        "PMS_PLNAME_RANDOM_MUSIC": "यादृच्छिक संगीत",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_ARTIST": "{} द्वारा संगीत",
        "PMS_PLNAME_SONG": "{song} by {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_ALBUM": "{artist} का {album} एल्बम",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_GENRE": "{} संगीत",
        "PMS_PLNAME_PLAYLIST": "{} प्लेलिस्ट"
    },
    "ar-SA": {
        "SKILL_WELCOME": "مرحباً بك في AskPlex. ماذا ترغب في فعله؟",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_REPROMPT": "ماذا ترغب في فعله؟",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK": "مرحباً بك في AskPlex، كنت تستمع إلى {}. هل ترغب في المتابعة؟",
        "SKILL_WELCOME_PLAYBACK_REPROMPT": "هل ترغب في المتابعة؟",
        "SKILL_HELP": "يتصل AskPlex بخادم Plex الخاص بك، يمكنك طلب الموسيقى حسب الفنان أو الألبوم أو النوع، بالإضافة إلى الأغاني والقوائم التشغيل المحددة.",
        "SKILL_INTENT_SLOTS_MISSING": "آسف، لم أفهم ذلك.",
        "SKILL_EXCEPTION": "آسف، حدث خطأ داخلي.",
        "SKILL_DEVICE_NOT_SUPPORTED": "آسف، هذا الجهاز غير مدعوم.",
        "SKILL_SONG_DETAILS": "هذه هي {song} من {artist}.",
        "PMS_CONNECTION_ERROR": "آسف، حدث خطأ أثناء الاتصال بخادم Plex.",
        "PMS_SECTION_ERROR": "آسف، حدث خطأ أثناء البحث عن القسم {}.",
        "PMS_SECTION_NOT_FOUND": "آسف، لا أستطيع العثور على القسم {}.",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_ERROR": "آسف، حدث خطأ أثناء البحث عن الموسيقى.",
        "PMS_TRACKS_SEARCH_EMPTY": "آسف، لا أستطيع العثور على الموسيقى في مجموعتك.",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "آسف، حدث خطأ أثناء البحث عن {}.",
        "PMS_ARTIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "آسف، لا أستطيع العثور على {} في مجموعتك.",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_ERROR": "آسف، حدث خطأ أثناء البحث عن الأغنية {song} من {artist}.",
        "PMS_SONG_SEARCH_EMPTY": "آسف، لا أستطيع العثور على الأغنية {song} من {artist} في مجموعتك.",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_ERROR": "آسف، حدث خطأ أثناء البحث عن الألبوم {album} من {artist}.",
        "PMS_ALBUM_SEARCH_EMPTY": "آسف، الألبوم {album} من {artist} لا يحتوي على أي مسارات.",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_ERROR": "آسف، حدث خطأ أثناء البحث عن موسيقى {}.",
        "PMS_GENRE_SEARCH_EMPTY": "آسف، لا أستطيع العثور على موسيقى {} في مجموعتك.",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_ERROR": "آسف، حدث خطأ أثناء البحث عن القائمة التشغيل {}.",
        "PMS_PLAYLIST_SEARCH_EMPTY": "آسف، لا أستطيع العثور على القائمة التشغيل {}.",
        "PMS_PLAYING": "تشغيل {} في AskPlex.",
        "PMS_PLNAME_RANDOM_MUSIC": "موسيقى عشوائية",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_ARTIST": "موسيقى من {}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_SONG": "{song} من {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_ALBUM": "ألبوم {album} من {artist}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_MUSIC_BY_GENRE": "موسيقى {}",
        "PMS_PLNAME_PLAYLIST": "قائمة التشغيل {}"
    }
}